<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Final Project - Natural Language Processing - S18 -->
<!-- AXYZ group -->
<!-- Xinyang Zhu / 2021409044 / XXZ170001 / xyzhu@utdallas.edu / (469)-974-7431 -->
<!-- Alvin Zhang / YXZ165231 -->

<!-- These are faqs used in our project -->
<!-- It's a questions collection base on Amazon Echo 2nd edition on amazon.com -->
<!-- Most of questions (0-49) are user asked questions by "most helpful", with minimal data cleaning. -->
<!-- Some questions (50- ) are questions I made of, mostly basic information about Echo. -->

<faqs>
    <entry id="0">
        <question>
            Does it have a rechargeable battery inside?
        </question>
        <answer>
            All Echo's are corded, not battery powered.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="1">
        <question>
            Can I use Alexa to make phone calls through my iPhone, or does it do it some other way?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes. Amazon has setup it's own VOIP system, which is what makes the calls. It's completely free to call
            anyone, you can just specify the phone number you want to call or say a name from your address book. It uses
            the called I'd of our cellphone so that people see the call is from you. A good comparison would be Skype
            calling.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="2">
        <question>
            Can I request any song to play?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Echo Music: WiFi and an Amazon Account is required. It does not have to be a Prime account. The Echo's will
            default to the free Amazon Music. In Alexa Setup, Skills listed that you can enable:

            1. Amazon Music (free) default, auto enables
            2. Prime Music (Prime Member) auto enables
            3. Pandora (free, link your own account))
            4. TuneIn (free)
            5. iHeart (free)
            6. Amazon Music Unlimited (subscription)
            7. Spotify (subscription)
            8. Sirius XM (subscription)

            None of the enabled music Skills are required. TuneIn and iHeart will allow you to specify radio stations
            when commanding Alexa, both real and fabricated. If you do nothing, you will still have Amazon Music for
            free.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="3">
        <question>
            Can it play the music favorites I have in my iTunes account?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You can. There is a skill you can enable called “my media” in the Alexa app. It allows you to basically link
            your home media or iTunes account on your computer. Once that’s done, you just say, “Alexa open my media and
            play The Beatles” for instance. It works great for me and we have Apple Music so there’s a lot of music.
            Hope this helps.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="4">
        <question>
            Need your phone number to help set up alexa?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You do not need a phone number to setup the Echo, but you do need a smart phone or tablet with cell service
            to setup the calling service with drop in.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="5">
        <question>
            Is the only difference between echo and dot the speaker?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, that the only difference.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="6">
        <question>
            Do you have to have Amazon Prime?
        </question>
        <answer>
            There seems to be some confusion about this. The answer depends on what you want your echo to do.
            Most of its features don't require Amazon Prime at all. You just need a smartphone that can use the Alexa
            app, a wifi connection, and an Amazon account.
            Some features, however, do require Amazon Prime. These are things like Amazon Prime Music, which require
            Prime, but can be accessed through other means than the echo.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="7">
        <question>
            What is a Zigbee hub?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Zigbee is a wireless protocol used by many smart home products. The Hub acts like a middle man, allowing
            your Zigbee smart home devices to talk to other devices like the Echo Plus. You can sort of think of it like
            a translator that allows devices to communicate across platforms.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="8">
        <question>
            Does alexa listen in on my conversations since it's always connected to the web?
        </question>
        <answer>
            No, the listening circuit is on the Echo device. When the device detects the wake work "Alexa" it begins
            streaming your command to the Alexa Voice Service on the Amazon Cloud (web). It records your commands and
            Alexa's response and saves them on your Amazon account. This helps Alexa "learn" your speech
            characteristics. You can see (and play and delete) these recordings in the Alexa app. Not to worry. :)
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="9">
        <question>
            Will it work with 220v electricity?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Much like most electronics (cell phone, laptop, tablets, etc.), the included power supply is 110-240v and as
            long as you have the proper adapter for the plug in your country of choice, it is fine. I can confirm this
            as I just took my Alexa to the Philippines and did not need a transformer. I left her there with my son to
            use in his condo.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="10">
        <question>
            Can be used internationally?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You can use it wherever you have wifi access. But only a few languages are supported atm.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="11">
        <question>
            Does Alexa Echo require the regular use of a smartphone?
        </question>
        <answer>
            For the first time how do I set up my alexa.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="12">
        <question>
            Whats the difference between this and the plus?
        </question>
        <answer>
            The primary functional differences are that that the Plus includes a Zigbee Hub and has a larger tweeter.
            Physically, the Plus is similar to the 1st Generation Echo in size, shape and overall look and doesn't have
            interchangeable outer shells.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="13">
        <question>
            Can I use echo to type a book manuscript?
        </question>
        <answer>
            No
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="14">
        <question>
            Does Echo have FM radio?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, you can stream both AM and FM radio stations.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="15">
        <question>
            Can I buy it here and use it in a another country like Israel?
        </question>
        <answer>
            As long as you have wireless internet and you download the Alexa app on your portable device i.e. phone,
            tablet then you should be fine. My only concern would be how it connects to electric, as the device itself
            is not electric. I know outlets in Germany are much different than the U.S. so make sure you look that up
            and get what you need for converting to their outlets before you go.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="16">
        <question>
            Does it stream Siriusxm?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="17">
        <question>
            When I am not home, can I send a message to the echo from my cellphone and have it tell my wife, "I'm
            calling you, go find your cell phone."?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes this has been very useful for that reason. You can also just call the device from your iPhone app and if
            wife says "Alexa answer" you can talk over the speaker..... and help her work out work out where she left
            her phone this time!!
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="18">
        <question>
            If I have alexa app from 1st generation echo do I need to download app again to set up 2nd generation?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Are you referring to the phone app or to an Alexa "skill?" The phone app is simply the Alexa app and is the
            same no matter which Echo device(s) you own or what generation they are. As for the Alexa skills, once
            enabled they will work with any Echo device (though of course you'll need an Echo Show or Echo Spot to get
            full functionality from any skills that utilize a screen).

            The great thing about Alexa skills is that they run on Amazon's cloud, not your actual Echo device. So as
            Amazon adds skills to Alexa they automatically become available to you, and as skills themselves get updated
            you will automatically be running the most up-to-date version.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="19">
        <question>
            How do I install it?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You plug it in to the wall, download the Alexa app and through the app you connect it to your Wi-Fi. Pretty
            easy.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="20">
        <question>
            I don't have have Wi-Fi?
        </question>
        <answer>
            If you have a modem you can add a decent WiFi router for about $17. Then you'll have WiFi. (Check the Tenda
            router if interested.)
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="21">
        <question>
            So, an echo still requires to pay $3.99 month to play amazon music unlimited?
        </question>
        <answer>
            I was not aware of that...will check it out...thanks.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="22">
        <question>
            Can Alexa work with 220 volts?
        </question>
        <answer>
            The Echo only plugs into 110 V, the Eco Dot plugs into the computer/laptop USB
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="23">
        <question>
            My new 2nd generation Echo does not have voice recognition available through the app on my iPad, why?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Pretty sure the Voice Profile can only be set up on a smartphone.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="24">
        <question>
            Can you simplify commands - example: "alexa, play wcco radio". versus "alexa, play 8.30 wcco am radio
            through InTune"?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Is there only one radio station in Waco? Probably not. I find that after giving Alexa a detailed command
            (wordy) for a while it seems to "learn" keywords and I can shorten the command significantly. So maybe after
            giving the longer command a few times you can say "Alexa, play MY Waco radio". Alexa does involve AI.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="25">
        <question>
            Can the material skin of the new generation 2 Echo be removed? Is there the traditional black plastic cover
            beneath that?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, you can remove the cover, which Amazon calls a "shell", for cleaning or to change it out for another
            one.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="26">
        <question>
            I need to reset mine because it will not connect to wifi. there is no reset button and i’ve tried holding
            down the microphone and volume down button.
        </question>
        <answer>
            I disconnect the plug from my Echo devices when they lose wifi; doing that resets them. I forgot the proper
            way to reset but when I originally tried that, it didn't work. So, unplugging echo connection Cord (attached
            to echo) and then plugging back in is what works for me. Unplugging the electric connect from the outlet and
            then plugging back in might work too.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="27">
        <question>
            will Echo control any smart TV?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Broadlink makes a device they call the Black Bean. It can be added as a skill to the Echo and will act as a
            smart remote. It emits 360deg IR, and can learn from most remotes. This will not work if you device uses an
            RF connection, but very few do, so should not be an issue.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="28">
        <question>
            Is echo portable?
        </question>
        <answer>
            I have moved it from an upstairs room to down stairs. That is all.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="29">
        <question>
            Can the echo pair with more than one pair of Bluetooth speakers?
        </question>
        <answer>
            That’s a good question and I’m going to give you a half answer. I’m pretty sure only one Bluetooth at a
            time, HOWEVER, you can join multiple echoes, dots, shows , etc to create a GROUP that plays the same thing
            simultaneously wherever they are on your home network. Understand one thing important!!: if you have a
            Bluetooth speaker with a device that is part of that group, using the group will kick the Bluetooth speaker
            off. Only the Amazon products connect to each other and play simultaneously. Good luck!
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="30">
        <question>
            Can I use this like an alarm clock where I can tell it to come on and play a preset fm station to wake me up
            in the morning?
        </question>
        <answer>
            It is easy to do. Ask Alexa to wake you at a certain time and in my case I just gave her a time and she
            responded with is that morning or afternoon. I responded with AM and at the designated time I got a musical
            note arrangement. Kinda neat. However I have not asked for a particular song to play.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="31">
        <question>
            How do I connect lights to the Echo?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You need to have one of the following: Alexa-compatible Smart bulb, Alexa-compatible Smart plug, or
            Alexa-compatible Smart switch.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="32">
        <question>
            what is the major difference between amazon echo (2nd gen) and Echo Plus?
        </question>
        <answer>
            is there a cost to just listen to music
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="33">
        <question>
            If we install the landlines option will we "still have to have" a smartphone with cell service to setup
            calling with drop in to function properly?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Can Echo connect to Bose speaker? (as an Echo Dot can do)
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="34">
        <question>
            can you Bluetooth echo to your wifi?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You can but not with the group function, whole house needs to hard wired.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="35">
        <question>
            Tell me about the connection to an external amplifier. What's required both ends?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You can connect via Bluetooth or with a cable by the 3.5mm stereo jack on the Echo. If you plan to leave it
            connected you might consider the less expensive Dot which is identical to the Echo except for size. So, on
            the Echo/Dot side, Bluetooth or 3.5mm plug. On the amp/receiver/external speaker side, whatever connection
            is compatible. Most have an "aux in" which is usually 3.5mm also. Sometimes RCA plugs (yellow and white.)
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="36">
        <question>
            What is the warranty on the echo 2nd generation? I ordered from Amazon.
        </question>
        <answer>
            The Echo comes with a 1-year limited warranty and service included. Optional 1-year, 2-year, and
            3-year extended warranty available for U.S. Customers sold separately.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="37">
        <question>
            If I have two Echos in same room for added sound will they both respond and play music in sync ?
        </question>
        <answer>
            No. All Echo devices use what Amazon calls "Echo Spatial Perception" which is a fancy way to say that if
            more than one Echo device hears your request, they can work out which device is the closest to you and only
            that one will respond.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="38">
        <question>
            Can wife and me use Alexa?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, more than one person can use Alexa, there is even a voice recognition capability.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="39">
        <question>
            Is the power cord still black on the new color Echo 2's?
        </question>
        <answer>
            yes, I have 2 of them and they both are black.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="40">
        <question>
            I run robust wi-fi security. The passcode is quite lengthy. Could this be an issue? Can't use nest w/o
            shortening the code.
        </question>
        <answer>
            I have a lengthy passcode as well and it worked just fine.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="41">
        <question>
            Will echo dot and echo work separately on same wi-fi? eg play different radio stations at the same time?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes it will. Except that it will play Prime music on only one at a time. Pandora and iHeartRadio will play
            on multiple Echo devices.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="42">
        <question>
            Does it speak Portuguese?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Not yet, no. Current language options are English, German and Japanese.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="43">
        <question>
            Why does it say the alexa network is unsecured
        </question>
        <answer>
            Not sure. Maybe your wifi connection is not password protected? Be sure you have a password. Other than
            that, do not know what it means.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="44">
        <question>
            Can I unplug it and still listen to music?
        </question>
        <answer>
            If you want to use without having to worry about having a plug handy, check out the Tap. You charge it on a
            base and can then take it anywhere without worrying about a plug. I use mine all over the house and yard. It
            now has voice control so you do not have to push the button to communicate.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="45">
        <question>
            I just opened the box for an echo ii, and there is no power cord. is it supposed to have one included?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Yes, it is normally in a small potion of the black interior "package/box". I have purchased two Echos and
            one Echo Dot and all three came with a power cord.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="46">
        <question>
            I do not own a smart phone but have a computer Windows 10. Can I use the echo with this?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You can do the basic setup with a browser: http://alexa.amazon.com The smartphone app is necessary to enable
            Alexa Calling features.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="47">
        <question>
            Is the wood better more durable than the cloth one?
        </question>
        <answer>
            I like the the cloth version but depends on the taste I guess
            To me it hides better the dirt and the material looks durable.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="48">
        <question>
            So will this stand on its own or do I need Alexa for it to work?
        </question>
        <answer>
            You need Alexa, which is free.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="49">
        <question>
            How to check battery level?
        </question>
        <answer>
            there are add on rechargeable bases.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <!-- Following are questions made up -->

    <entry id="50">
        <question>
            What's the price? How much is it?
        </question>
        <answer>
            It's $99.99. Buy 2 and save $30. Add 2 Echo (2nd Generation) devices to your cart and automatically receive
            $30 off. Or 5 monthly payments of $20.00.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="51">
        <question>
            What are the color options?
        </question>
        <answer>
            We have Charcoal Fabric, Heather Gray Fabric, Oak Finish, Sandstone Fabric, Walnut Finish.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="52">
        <question>
            What are the color options?
        </question>
        <answer>
            We have Charcoal Fabric, Heather Gray Fabric, Oak Finish, Sandstone Fabric, Walnut Finish.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="53">
        <question>
            How to play music?
        </question>
        <answer>
            The 2nd generation Echo has a 2.5” downward-firing woofer and 0.6” tweeter powered by Dolby to deliver crisp
            vocals and dynamic bass throughout the room. You can play music from Amazon Music, Spotify, Pandora,
            iHeartRadio, TuneIn, and more. With Amazon Music, you can search by lyrics, time-period, or let Alexa pick
            the music for you. Set a music alarm to wake up to your favorite song or playlist. You can also listen to
            audiobooks from Audible, podcasts, radio stations, news briefs, and more.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="54">
        <question>
            If I have more than one Echo, how to play music in different rooms?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Want to play music on an Echo in another room? Now with multi-room music, you can tell Alexa to play across
            your compatible Echo devices. Tell Alexa to play jazz in the kitchen, top pop in the family room, or play
            the same song throughout your whole home.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="55">
        <question>
            How to control home devices like light or TV?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Use Echo to switch on the lamp before getting out of bed, turn on the coffee maker on your way to the
            kitchen, or dim the lights from the couch to watch a movie—all without lifting a finger. Ask Alexa to turn
            on the TV, turn up the volume, change the channel, or play your favorite movie. Echo can control your Amazon
            Fire TV and select devices from Sony, Dish, and Logitech.

            Control multiple devices at scheduled times or with a single voice command, like locking the doors and
            turning off the lights when you go to bed. Echo works with lights, locks, switches, thermostats, and more
            from WeMo, Philips Hue, SmartThings, Insteon, Nest, ecobee, and Wink.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="56">
        <question>
            How to talk or message to people with Echo?
        </question>
        <answer>
            With Echo, you can talk to almost anyone hands-free—no tapping or searching required. Use the Drop In
            feature when you want to connect instantly with compatible Echo devices in your home. For example, you can
            ask someone for help with a chore, or remind the kids to go to sleep—without having to raise your voice.
            With Alexa Announcements you can also use Echo to broadcast a quick, one-way message to all other Echo
            devices in your home.

            Making calls with Alexa is easy. Your contacts will see your number when they receive the call so they know
            who is calling. Set up your voice profile and teach Alexa to recognize your voice. When you say, “Alexa,
            call Mom”, Alexa will call your mom, even if you have multiple users in your home. Additionally, you can
            send messages via voice or text to anyone with a supported Echo device or the Alexa App.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="57">
        <question>
            How can it recognize my voice? How to use it?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Tucked under the light ring is an array of seven microphones that use beamforming technology and enhanced
            noise cancellation. The 2nd generation Echo has improved wake-word performance to hear you ask a question
            from any direction—even in noisy environments or while playing music at loud volumes.

            When you want to use Echo, simply say the wake word, “Alexa,” and Echo lights up and connects to the cloud,
            where the Alexa Voice Service recognizes and responds to your request instantly. Learn more about voice
            recognition on Echo.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="58">
        <question>
            What else can it do?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Echo uses tens of thousands of skills and counting. Skills add even more capabilities like ordering a pizza
            from Domino's, requesting a ride from Uber, tracking your fitness with Fitbit, controlling your TV with
            Dish, and more. To enable new skills, just ask Alexa.

            New skills are being added all the time. You can also see ratings and reviews to learn what other customers
            are saying about the thousands of skills available in the Alexa App.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="59">
        <question>
            What's the difference between versions of Echo? Compare Echo devices.
        </question>
        <answer>
            Besides price, for Echo Dot, Echo, Echo plus, the main difference is the speaker, and Echo plus has a
            built-in hub for simple setup of compatible smart home devices. Echo Spot and Echo Show has screen,
            difference is the size of screen.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="60">
        <question>
            What's the size and weight?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Device size (actual size and weight may vary): 1.3" x 3.3" x 3.3", 5.7 oz. (32 mm x 84 mm x 84 mm, 163
            grams)
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="61">
        <question>
            What's the Wi-Fi hardware and connectivity?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Dual-band Wi-Fi supports 802.11 a/b/g/n (2.4 and 5 GHz) networks. Does not support connecting to ad-hoc (or
            peer-to-peer) Wi-Fi networks.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="62">
        <question>
            What's the Bluetooth hardware and connectivity?
        </question>
        <answer>
            Advanced Audio Distribution Profile (A2DP) support for audio streaming from your mobile device to Echo or
            from Echo to your Bluetooth speaker. Audio/Video Remote Control Profile (AVRCP) for voice control of
            connected mobile devices. Hands-free voice control is not supported for Mac OS X devices. Bluetooth speakers
            requiring PIN codes are not supported.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="63">
        <question>
            What's the audio specification?
        </question>
        <answer>
            2.5” (63.5 mm) woofer and 0.6” (16 mm) tweeter.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="64">
        <question>
            How to find the Alexa App?
        </question>
        <answer>
            The Alexa App is compatible with Fire OS, Android, and iOS devices. You can find it on App Store or Google
            Play store.
        </answer>
    </entry>

    <entry id="65">
        <question>
            How is the sound quality?
        </question>
        <answer>
            This latest model is better sound quality than old versions.
        </answer>
    </entry>

</faqs>